♪♪
[ Click ]
-[ Groaning ]
[ Groans ]
[ Indistinct shouting ]
-Come on, man.
Give me some fucking help.
I'm dying right now.
-Sign right there.
Nah. You're getting blood
all over it.
Lucky I brought another copy.
Sign with your left hand...
right there.
Well...
I'm sure there's something
you want to say
in your own defense.
♪♪
-♪ I'm tryna see
all my niggas with jewels ♪
♪ And yet I can't always
afford food ♪
♪ That's the type of nigga
that I am ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm dumb as shit,
but I got a plan ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm wylin'
with my money ♪
♪ And my mouth
finna look sunny ♪
♪ I'll smoke the profit
off a flip, nigga ♪
♪ Please know I do not
give a shit, nigga ♪
♪ I want Florida perm cuts
on all of my teeth ♪
♪ Niggas with just one cap
won't be fuckin' with me ♪
♪ Trillion cut, give no fuck,
I know I'm not ugly ♪
♪ With a mouth full of slugs,
I'm on my Ron Weasley ♪
♪ I want Florida perm cuts
on all of my teeth ♪
♪ Niggas with just one cap
won't be fuckin' with me ♪
♪ Trillion cut, give no fuck,
I know I'm not ugly ♪
♪ With a mouth full of slugs,
I'm on my Ron Weasley ♪
♪ Finna act a bigger dick
than all Jim Crow's kids ♪
♪ I lost all sense
and sensibility ♪
♪ At the trenches' entrance ♪
♪ Life got no meaning
outside of the stimulus ♪
♪ And the money flip, whippin'
down Washington in the Prius ♪
♪ Looking, oh, so suspicious,
fortunes every week ♪
♪ And niggas ain't never
spun no wheel ♪
♪♪
♪ I put the chain
in game changer for real ♪
♪ A quarter off the flip,
and I ain't even ♪
♪ Broke open my last seal ♪
-So?
What's good?
Lil' Rip?
-Hey, man, put a "C"
on the beginning
of that shit next time.
-What you gonna do?
Show me what you gonna do.
-Mnh. Mnh. Hold on.
I got you something.
-What?
-I got you something.
-Show me after.
-Hold on. Just chill. Hold on.
Tell me you're not
proposing right now.
-Nah, I ain't proposing.
This -- It's a gift.
I mean, it is a ring, though.
[ Tuts ]
This is my mom's.
It's just some Zulu shit.
You know?
I thought it was kinda cool.
-[ Chuckles ] I, um...
Damn. I -- I thought
you knew what this was.
Us just having fun
or whatever.
I mean...that's not all it is,
but my ass can't be seen
with no Crip.
And I damn sure can't be
wearing his jewelry around.
You feel me?
-I know that shit.
That's why
we should fucking leave.
Get our own spot where it ain't
all this gang shit, man.
That shit exhausting.
-Yeah.
I'm gonna need you
to take your Zulu ring...
and get the fuck out my ride.
[ Vehicle approaches ]
[ Siren chirps ]
-For real?
[ Police radio chatter ]
-Zarina Shannon,
exit the vehicle.
Step out now,
or we start firing!
♪♪
-Come on. Nice and slow.
-Let's go!
Come on!
♪♪
-We ain't even on set.
What is y'all doing?
-Turn around
and face the other way.
Get your hands on the hood.
-Where is your bodycam at?
-What you doing, homeboy?
You're not reaching
for that piece, are you?
-Bitch-ass piece.
-What are you doing with this?
If I search this car,
I'm not gonna find any drugs?
-Do it look like
there's drugs in the car?
-It does look like
there's drugs in the car.
-All right.
Well, you at it, so check it.
-Get him out here now!
♪♪
You stay put.
-[ Clears throat ]
-It's loaded.
♪♪
-If you want in Night Patrol,
this is it.
♪♪
-Shit!
-Look at him go!
Run, boy!
-Go get him!
♪♪
-[ Grunts ]
The fuck?!
[ Gun cocks ]
♪♪
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You don't have to do this.
You don't gotta do this.
Hey, hey, just hold up.
Hold up, hold up, hold up!
♪♪
-[ Slurps ]
When I was a kid,
all I wanted to do was be a cop.
I just thought
it was the coolest thing.
Or lit. [ Chuckles ]
I thought it was lit.
But, um,
I know the way you see cops
is not the way it was for me.
We're portrayed differently now
in the media and in movies.
We're seen in a very specific
light, often a negative light.
And there are a few
bad apples out there.
I'm not gonna discount that.
But I'm here to tell you
that most of us are good.
Okay? We're good apples.
Now, why do they even
have us out there in the world?
What do they pay us for?
Well, unfortunately, there are
a lot of people out there
who are not so good.
[ Rap music playing ]
-Yeah!
-Oh, God.
-Yeah! Y'all know what it is!
Y'all know what it is!
-Okay. Uh-oh.
-What's up?!
-[ Gun cocks ]
-You don't have to do this!
[ All screaming ]
-Hope y'all prayed
to a higher power today!
I hope you fucking prayed
Hey, you. Yeah, you.
I guess I'm gonna break
my dick off for you, cuh.
-What?
-Get your bitch ass down here.
Did I stutter?
Hurry the fuck up!
Did I stutter?!
Kneel the fuck down!
Did I say get up?!
♪♪
Why don't you put your thumb
in your mouth?
Put your motherfucking thumb
in your mouth, nigga.
And work that shit.
Like we bumped up in Chino.
-♪ Now I'm in the pen ♪
-Slower, nigga. Slower, nigga!
-Okay.
-That was great.
That was fun, wasn't it?
[Chuckling] That was great!
Okay. How about a...
big round of applause here?
Just a demonstration.
All fun. It's okay.
You're -- You're okay.
Fucking blanks? Inside a school?
-[ Scoffs ]
-Brass is gonna have your badge
for that cowboy shit.
-Brass wanted me
on juvie intervention.
I think I intervened.
-Yeah, that's great.
-Whether you know it or not,
them little niggas gonna
piss their pants the next time
they even think about
stealing a pack of gum.
Mission accomplished.
-Yeah.
What's the fucking mission?
Don't do that. Don't do that.
-Proactive policing, sir.
Stings like a bitch.
-I got it. See ya!
♪♪
-♪ I bang
'til the bang is gone ♪
♪ I bang for the cause,
I bang for the dawgs ♪
♪ I bang for the gangsta hoes ♪
♪ I bang for Pasadena rose ♪
♪ I bang on a bitch,
and I click, I'm gone ♪
♪ I chose to bang
when I R-A-P ♪
-You know, I told you
we don't have to keep it formal,
so you can --
you can cut the "sir" shit.
It's getting a little annoying.
-What, you just one of the boys?
Is that what this is? Like...
We're all in the same,
sucking shit together?
That's -- That's your style?
-Something like that.
-♪ I chose to bang
'cause bangers love beef ♪
♪ I bang the heat,
I bang for free ♪
-[ Siren chirps ]
-Pull over to the curb
right now!
Stop. Engine off!
-♪ 'Til you cop a plea ♪
♪ I put the B in B-A-N-G ♪
-So is that how
y'all did it in Spec Ops?
Just back-to-back,
dumping hella mags, yelling,
spraying up Charlie and shit?
-Something like that.
-♪ All I do is
bang, bang, bang ♪
♪ Come through,
hittin' corners ♪
[ Siren chirps ]
♪ All you hear is
"bang-bang-bang" ♪
♪ For all my fallen soldiers ♪
-Stop running!
-Suspect fleeing on foot!
-You the one
that wet up bin Laden.
You can tell me.
I ain't gonna tell nobody.
You on some John Rambo,
Michael Dudikoff shit.
-Still not exactly clear
what ninjas have to do
with being a Scout Sniper,
but...
I'm impressed that you threw in
a Michael Dudikoff reference.
You gotta be the only Crip
that knows Michael Dudikoff.
-Well, we got
a sleeper shift to burn,
so plenty of time
for some 'Nam flashbacks.
-Ah, great.
-[ Screams ]
Is that -- Did that...
Yeah!
-♪ Whether buster, banger,
bitch, I'll bang on 'em all ♪
♪ Disrespect your whole hood,
bang on the wall ♪
♪ Bang in courts and malls,
don't never think you safe ♪
-Why don't we talk about
your sordid past instead?
-Ah! Boo!
-Yeah, that's what I thought.
-You fucking suck!
-That's what I thought.
-Hey.
-Still can't believe
they got you working juvie.
You were a P2. What a waste.
-I made it out of the Courts.
Once a Crip, always a Crip.
-No. Fuck that. You're a cop.
You know your shit.
And you're not fucking off
like an asshole.
♪♪
-Thank you.
-♪ Bang-bang-bang ♪
-That means a lot coming from a
genuine Navy SEAL like yourself.
-♪ Bang-bang-bang ♪
Sir.
-Christ.
Three months
riding around together,
we must've eaten here,
what, 600 times?
Y-You're not sick
of this torta truck yet?
-[ Xavier laughs ]
-All right.
[ Siren chirps ]
-Whoo-hoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
-The police!
-Whoo!
[ Speaking Spanish ]
Uh, yo, Carr, let me --
let me run something by you.
-Shoot.
-I was running a street name,
gang name, whatever,
and I'm coming up blank.
You come across a "Cripboi"
in your previous day job?
-Uh, why would you offer salsa
if you're gonna give us just
one little container of salsa?
-I don't know, man.
It's just how they do it.
They give you one salsa.
Who cares?
Let it go. Let it go.
Cripboi?
-Cripboi? Crip -- Uh...
[ Chuckles ]
-What?
-With a "I"?
-There's a tag I came across.
Got me curious.
But, um, thought
you might know off the top.
Cancel it.
I'll -- I'll keep digging.
-It's just funny because, um,
it's my brother's gamer handle
from back in the day.
-Oh.
-Let me hit him up.
I'll -- I'll ask him.
-All right. Yeah. Make the call.
I'll handle this.
I'll handle the important shit,
all right?
-All right.
-You just have to know
how to speak the language
of the working man.
Amigo!
-All right, partner.
[ Speaking Spanish ]
-I speak Spanish, motherfucker!
-Yeah?
-Hey. You got a minute?
-Uh, nah, not really.
[ Sighs ] You good?
You sound -- You sound weird.
♪♪
-I ain't got time
for this right now, Zay.
-Oh. Packed day
of doing fuck-all?
You just sitting around
at Ayanda's house
with your thumb up your ass?
-Would you start giving him
extra salsas, please?
-What's good?
Are you in trouble?
-You really calling me to ask me
if I'm in trouble
right now, Zay,
or are you just trying
to be in my business?
-Y-You're fine. You're --
We'll leave it at that.
You're good.
So, look, I'm calling, uh,
calling about a A.K.A.
You ever heard of a "Cripboi"?
I got PD asking me about it,
and, uh, it sounds like
something serious.
-Uh, hey, I gotta --
Uh, I gotta go, all right?
I-I'm gonna hit you later.
-Well, I --
-[ Beep ]
♪♪
-Fuck.
-On your bitch ass!
Yo! Bitch-ass Crips!
Hey, yo, yo! What up, bitch?!
-You in Blood territory, fool!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
♪♪
[ Line ringing ]
[ Indistinct ]
-[ Grunts ]
♪♪
-Fuck you want, nigga?
-I came to see Bornelius.
♪♪
-[ Chuckle ] See me?
[ Whirring ]
You see deez nuts, nigga.
Little nigga, I should shoot
your fucking dick off.
You been sniffing after
my little sister again?
No, no, no, no. Let me guess.
You're here to beg
for me not to kill you
and all them lil' crab niggas
from your hood
for my fallen soldiers, right?
-Hey, hey.
-Right?
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa. Hey.
-I can't stand
you Zulu motherfuckers.
-I just came to tell you...
LAPD shot your sister.
I think it was maybe
Night Patrol.
-[ Scoffs ] L-- LAP--
Nigga, I'll shoot you
right now, nigga.
-No, no, no!
Look, look, look, look!
They -- They knew
where she would be, all right,
when they did that shit!
♪♪
-Man, check this nigga over
real quick, man.
[ Detector warbling ]
LAPD. What the fuck
is you talking about, man?
[ Detector warbling ]
What the crystal saying?
-He's human.
-All right.
-But he damn sure ain't Piru.
-Well, let me check his aura.
-What, you out here
infiltrating the set, nigga?
-Man, no!
-I know.
Maybe...
Illuminati.
One of these old shape-shifting,
reptilian-worshipping-ass,
microchip-planting-ass niggas.
-Hmm.
-Hey. Look.
Preem said that
y'all was into y'all
"conspiriocracies" and shit,
but, nigga, you sound dumb.
I pray y'all minds
ain't so sherm-fried
that y'all
won't just listen to me!
All right?! Hear me out!
-I'm gonna ask you one time,
my nigga.
You sell Primo
out to the police?
-No. I did not.
-Then why the fuck you here
and my sister dead then, nigga?!
Huh? Huh?!
Huh?!
-Yeah, nigga.
Why they ain't kill
your bitch ass, too?
-Look. I don't fucking know.
I don't know.
They just -- They just didn't.
♪♪
-You know something, nigga.
I'm gonna get to
the bottom of this shit.
♪♪
[ Groans ] Fuck!
[ Objects crashing ]
-Fuck.
♪♪
Night Patrol did this shit?
Fuck!
♪♪
-I didn't know
they did this to her.
♪♪
-Y'all feel that?
Residual satanic energy floating
all through this motherfucker.
A demon killed Preem.
-A demon? Fuck you mean a demon?
-A demon, nigga.
-Look like a leopard
did this shit on Piru.
-I ain't seen too many leopards
in the hood.
-Could have been
my shape-shifter.
They've been tracking one
in the area.
-Nah.
Last time I checked,
wasn't no shape-shifters
killing no Bloods.
-Not if they don't want me
to shape-shift a hole
in their motherfucking head.
♪♪
-It could be Lizard Man.
-True, true.
-You niggas
are fucking remedial.
LAPD did this.
I told y'all that shit!
-So what the fuck
is you saying, nigga?
This some LAPD Lizard Man shit?
Hmm?
♪♪
Fuck up.
-Looks like we got
chemical burns on there
from their acid tongues.
[ Primo laughs ]
♪♪
-Born, man, this shit fucked up.
-[ Sighs ]
Come on, man.
Bring that energy pyramid over.
♪♪
We ain't gonna leave her here in
this spiritually unclean shit.
Whatever killed Preem...
coming for us next.
♪♪
-[ Laughs ]
-Ah, shit's weak!
-Oh, not for you.
-Yeah, right.
-It's one of your better ones.
-Man...
♪♪
Hey, can you act
like you house-trained?
-Are you serious? It's a bar.
-No spitting on
the fucking floor, assholes!
-Oh, you got him doing --
Fucking Mr. Clean.
-Hawkins, you fucking dog, you.
-What?
-I ain't crashing
the going-away party, am I?
-Oh, hey, hey. No, no, no.
We're -- We're good.
-What'd you say?
-I owe you a congrats, hombre.
Gonna get you a beer.
-Get one for
my partner, too, huh?
Thanks a lot, Rivette.
-Hey. What that neo-Nazi say?
-Ah! Ha!
Got the bump.
Made Night Patrol.
-Oh, shit!
-Yeah.
-Wha-- Shit! That's...
Man! One year in,
you already made task force.
How many war crimes
I gotta commit to get my pin?
-It's not funny.
-You didn't tell him yet,
did you?
-I was working up to it.
-Ah, shit.
You know how it is, Carr.
Night Patrol likes 'em
mean and white.
-Oh, yeah?
But you're so nice!
You're, like,
one of the nice ones.
-I can't tell if you're joking.
-Yeah?
Well, look, man, it don't hurt
that you're also a war hero,
so congratulations, for real.
-Yeah?
All right.
Well, thanks, man.
-Yeah.
-Now, are we gonna
keep drinking cat piss
or can we get fucking drunk?!
Who wants shots?!
♪♪
[ Clanging ]
[ Chatter ]
♪♪
[ Keys jingling ]
[ Television playing ]
♪♪
-What the fuck?!
Damn.
-Where you been?
-Out. And about.
-Out and about?
What the fuck, Wazi?
You know you not
supposed to be out all night.
-All right, Ma. I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't --
-What the fuck is that, Wazi?!
You took this out of my room?!
You take this ring
out the Courts?
-Look, I didn't --
-Answer me right now.
Where did you go with it?
-We just --
-"We." Who is "we"?
-I met somebody when I was out.
-Fucking who was it, Wazi?
♪♪
-Primo.
-Piru Primo?
-Yeah.
♪♪
Police rolled up on us.
Ma, they shot her.
They shot her right there.
I know.
-Was it Night Patrol?
Gang Task Force?
Did they see you?
-Yes.
♪♪
-You done brought
sucking death down on us, boy.
You know that, right?
Night Patrol
is just getting started.
I seen this. They did
the same thing with your father.
What have I been screaming
at you since you was in diapers?
This shit is good versus evil.
The beast in the night
prowling in the dark,
with our blood, preying on the
righteous people of God's Earth!
♪♪
God!
This is...
We're fucked.
♪♪
[ Breathes deeply ]
We need to be ready.
♪♪
-[ Gunfire ]
-[ Plane engines roaring ]
[ Door opens ]
-Hey, big man.
Playing some games?
My buddy loves games.
-[ Gasping ]
♪♪
[ Siren chirps ]
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
♪♪
-Save it for the hunt.
[ Gunshots ]
-Damn.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Siren wails in distance ]
[ Dog barking ]
-Fuck.
Shit.
Fuck!
-Oof.
-Shut the fuck up.
Shut the -- Shut the fuck up.
-[ Chuckles ]
-You sniffing around
about a Cripboi
makes a whole lot of sense now.
Should make your bones chasing
around my little brother.
Huh? Partner?
-Here we go.
-What?
-[ Chuckles ]
I'm just fucking with you, dude.
-Mm-hmm.
You Night Patrol!
Puff your chest out!
Puff your
motherfucking chest out!
You're the LAPD Prince
of the varrio.
-[ Scoffs ]
-No?
-I don't get it.
What -- What is with you
and this hard-on
for making Night Patrol?
-I'm not hard.
I wasn't hard when I said that.
They're top dogs.
-That's what it is?
-Yes. Ain't -- Not that deep.
-Yeah.
-What? What's so wild
about me wanting to roll
with the big boys?
-Going from your neighborhood
to Gang Task Force
is a little wild.
What's that,
like the Crip version
of rebelling
against your parents?
-Something like that.
-Daddy was a Crip.
Cuh-rip! Cuh-rip!
He used to say that shit
when he walked in the house.
He got me in it...
Moms in it.
It's all family with the set.
-Hmm. Yeah, I bet.
-Well, my house
is a little different.
My moms blasting my pops
right in front of me.
They was arguing.
I don't even remember
what they was arguing about.
But my little brother, Wazi.
He was this baby.
He was crying.
-How old were you?
-I was 9.
I was tryin' to look out
for that little boy,
but he still stays with her.
And he believe
everything she says.
She's fucking crazy, dude,
on her African
mysticism bullshit.
Yeah, whatever she's been on,
she's been on it
ever since she killed my pops.
-Jesus Christ.
X, I didn't --
I didn't know that.
It's fucking awful.
I'm sure you've heard
what happened to my dad.
LAPD. Died in the line of...
Well, I bet you didn't know...
Dad was Night Patrol.
♪♪
-I did not know that.
-Yeah, they had something
to do with his death.
I know it.
We could never get
a straight story from brass.
-You doing all this
on some revenge shit?
-My dad was a good man.
He was a good cop. I know it.
-This is Night Patrol.
-Yeah.
-Do you hear what you're saying?
-They don't fuck around!
[ Siren chirps ]
-Fuck.
-LAPD! Fuck off!
-Hey!
[ Door opens ]
Hey!
-Hawkins, get in the car.
-Oh, shit.
[ Police radio chatter ]
-How'd you find me?
-Turn your radio on, shitbird.
You forget we work nights?
-That Cripboi shit?
It's my brother.
I'm fucking worried about him.
-I hear you.
I'll do what I can for him.
I'm still earning their trust.
♪♪
-Watch yourself, partner.
-Tell me something, Hawkins.
You seriously think
you're ready for Night Patrol?
-Are we still doing
this hazing bullshit?
Come on, man.
I popped your banger.
You got your dirt on me.
When are you gonna let me in
on the big secret around here?
Word's out. You guys are --
You're more than just good.
You're -- You're special.
I wanna be a part of that.
What -- You tell me.
What do -- What do I gotta do?
-Figured we'd clear
the air here, hoss.
-All right. Good.
-Sarge has got plans
for you, but...
I'm not buying the bullshit.
You're not the only one
with friends in Blackwater.
Yeah, it's all there.
At least enough
to paint the picture.
Favorite's Afghanistan.
Yeah, that part where
an entire camp of insurgents
end up with their heads on pikes
after ambushing your unit.
That's old-school payback.
But here's the thing.
Doesn't impress me.
Now, what I need
are team players in the field,
not some asshole
with his own agenda in my unit.
But...Sarge made the call.
Sarge wants you in.
So...here you are.
♪♪
All of these missions,
everything in here,
I was part of a team.
I'm a team player.
I promise you.
I won't be a problem for you.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-We'll see.
♪♪
-What's this?
-Sarge wants us
running down the kid
that slipped us on the 1-8-7.
-All right. Lead the way.
-I'm not going in there.
You are.
His bike's in the trunk.
Use it to get them
to open the door for you.
♪♪
[ Buzzer ]
[ Knock on door ]
-Evening, ma'am.
-You demons work fast.
-Ma'am, do you mind
if I step inside?
-If you think you can.
-Thank you.
I won't take up
too much of your time.
I'm just, uh --
I'm looking for your son Wazi.
Is he around?
-He here for you!
Just to talk to you.
-Here to bring him
his bike back, actually.
♪♪
Wazi.
-No, no, no, no, no!
[ Gunshot echoes ]
-I left your bike right there.
You left it somewhere
you shouldn't have been,
so I wanted you to have it,
if you need it.
And you use it.
Do you understand?
♪♪
-Anything else?
-That's all.
Thank you for your time.
I'll get out of your hair.
You have a lovely place.
Sorry for the intrusion.
[ Door opens and closes ]
♪♪
-Well?
-He wasn't home.
♪♪
[ Radio crackles ]
-Where's Hawkins?
Bring him to me.
It's time.
-I got him right here,
suited and booted.
He says he's ready to roll.
[ Chuckles ]
Even though he's got no
fucking idea what he's in for.
♪♪
[ Police radio chatter ]
-Ethan. My son.
I've waited so long
to bring you into the fold.
And to finally
see you in the flesh,
well...
it pleases me.
♪♪
You've come home now.
Here with your father again.
-[ Gasps ]
This is not real.
You're not real. You're dead.
I saw you die.
-I am reborn.
Bathed in the blood.
So shall you be.
[ Muffled laughter ]
-What'd you do?
-[ Laughs ]
-What did you do? You fuck!
You gave me a fucking drug.
[ Laughter ]
You're dead! You're dead!
-I'm so proud
of the man you've become.
I watched you.
I know how hard it was.
You suffered.
You lived with horror.
-[ Sobbing ]
I just don't understand. Dad.
-But you don't need
to struggle anymore.
You don't need to.
Your pain can simply vanish.
When you join me.
-What?
-When you join us.
You're standing on
the threshold of perfection.
-What the fuck?
-Death defeating death!
Will you be reborn in his image?
-Why are you talking like that?
What is going on?
I'm just --
-Hold him.
-No. What the fuck?!
What the fuck?
-When you take of the blood...
-What is this?
-...the same blood
that is now running
through our veins,
you, too, will be granted
everlasting life.
Be it his will.
-Don't do this.
Get the fuck off me!
[ Grunts ]
♪♪
-I've dreamt of this
for a long time.
♪♪
Now drink.
-[ Gagging ]
-You are the new link
in an imperishable chain.
You are the fine line
between civilization
and the unwashed.
♪♪
Drink, Ethan.
Drink.
And live forever, my son.
-[ Coughing ]
♪♪
Dad...
[ Gasps ]
♪♪
[ Chatter ]
-[ Door opens ]
-[ Camera shutter clicking ]
-[ Clears throat ]
Girls got the day off.
Come on in.
Let me guess.
You're throwing yourself
upon the mercy of the court
of my boot in your ass
for that Juvenile
Enforcement shitshow
I've been on calls about
for days now!
-Um, doughnuts?
-You know I'm pre-diabetic.
-I-I didn't.
-And there's also two missing.
Now, what do you want?
-I'm feeling a certain way
about being passed up
on Night Patrol for Hawkins
and, uh, just wanted to talk
to you for a minute about it.
♪♪
His father is a hero
around here.
There's a lot of good police
in his blood.
-I'm a better cop than Hawkins.
I just want my shot.
-You got a real future
in this department,
provided you don't
keep fucking it up.
Now...prove it.
♪♪
-Hmm. That waitress
with the titties?
Had to make
Officer Johnson stand down.
[ Chuckles ]
Tell me she didn't want it.
X?
-I guess.
-Ah, you were
all pouting and shit
'cause Hawkins
was breaking up with you,
but I know you saw it.
She was practically
begging for it.
-Yeah?
Begging for all
three and a half inches
of that Irish whiskey dick?
-Oh, fuck you, man.
That's it.
I'm planting crack
in the cruiser.
♪♪
[ Laughs ]
-Brass would probably
believe that shit, too.
-Let me tell you a little
something about chicks, Carr.
They don't always want
some baboon
cramming a firehose
up their twat.
They want dicks
genetically evolved
for their tight, white holes.
Lock and key, fucker.
[ Laughs ]
-Why you gotta
say shit like that?
-[ Laughs ]
♪♪
-♪ A mouth to feed
at the expense of ♪
♪ Both the partaker
and the partaken ♪
♪ An ignorant sacrifice that's
leading to the death of life ♪
♪ A savage slaughter,
a needless bloodbath ♪
-Is this the shit
you listen to?!
-♪ Why do we not see
through our greed? ♪
♪ This will lead
to the destruction ♪
-How you turn this shit off?
-It's a button.
It's a button on the top --
[ Music stops ]
-Get your ass
the fuck out of bed.
No more playing around.
I let you float
your entire life.
That shit over.
Now get up and help me
fortify the Courts
against these
gathered fucking demons.
Or, I swear...your ass
gonna be the first one they eat.
Done playin' with you.
♪♪
-♪ I had to change my life ♪
♪ Run for my life,
run for your life ♪
[ Chatter ]
-♪ Might fuck tonight ♪
-Excuse me.
Hey. Y'all got one
of these pamphlets?
[ Laughter ]
-Your mama been running around
like a chicken with no head.
-Mm-hmm.
-Oh, my.
She need to come to church.
-Hm!
-Yeah, don't I know it.
-[ Laughter ]
-Well, she said I'm supposed
to tell you to go inside
once you done
with your "chores."
[ Laughter ]
♪♪
-Wait, wait, wait. Your mama
got you on punishment?
-[ Laughter ]
-Ain't on no punishment.
I'm a grown man!
-Oh, okay.
-Wazi!
-Grown!
-Uh-oh.
-You been over
to the community center yet?!
We got people over there!
Or, if you done,
I need you inside!
Wazi?
[ Laughter ]
-Grown man walkin'!
-Go, Wazi!
-Go up there, Wazi! Get 'em!
[ Laughter ]
♪♪
[ Cellphone rings ]
-Get a horchata yet?
-They're sold out.
-Fuck!
-Yeah, Waz? I'm at work
right now. What's up?
-[ Sighs ]
-Yo, Wazi.
What you need, man?
♪♪
-All right. Um...
I -- The...
Maybe I mit--
Maybe I witnessed a murder.
-[ Sighs ] Fuck, Waz.
This wouldn't happen
to be that Piru lieutenant
I heard got smoked, would it?
-Can we talk about
this shit in person, X?
-Okay. Where you gonna be?
♪♪
-[Whispers] Fish spot.
-Meet me at the fish spot.
♪♪
-Fine.
Oh, and, Waz...
please don't make me
come looking for you.
-Fuck is a Waz? [ Spits ]
-My Crippin' ass little brother.
-Oh, yeah?
He out there "set trippin'"?
-Something like that.
-Fuck me!
-I remember my first sandwich.
-The fuck?!
Can I get a napkin?
♪♪
[ Chatter ]
-Rivette. Yo, do me a favor.
-You want me to hang back
like some fucking pre-pube boot
while you go lick NP scrote
to get in goods?
That about right?
-It's "pre-pubescent."
-Huh? What'd I say?
-"Pre-pubes."
-Yeah, before pubes. Pre-pube.
-You don't tell us
what to do, kid, all right?
-Xavier Carr.
Southeast Division.
-Where we are
currently standing.
-Patrol fucking rules!
-Uh, so, I'm partners with --
I was partnered with Hawkins,
and I got some intel on a case
he was -- he was working on.
Is he around?
-No.
-That's a shame.
Just tell you then.
Got a line on
your rider Piru shooter.
-Is that so?
-Very much so.
I'm from Colonial Courts.
I know the people.
I know what they're capable of.
A guy like me
could be useful to Task Force.
-Would you arrest
your own brother?
-I'm a cop. I arrest criminals.
-[ Chuckles ]
Well, then, why don't you
go do that, and we'll talk?
♪♪
[ Chatter ]
-Fucking Wazi.
-Jesus.
It's like the honeycomb hideout
for Crips.
Let's radio in a few units.
-No, we ain't
calling nobody yet.
That's just gonna
make matters worse.
If anything, I'll roll in myself
so nothing pops off.
-Partners don't let partners
stroll into the goddamn
viper's pit solo fucking dolo,
amigo.
-Partners don't take coke-headed
roaring monkeys
ready to pop shit off
when we're just trying
to take my brother out
in one fucking piece,
so stand down.
-Come on.
What is we even doing here?
-You are gonna shut your mouth
and follow my lead.
If your brother doesn't
help me get Night Patrol
off our fucking ass,
then I got no use for him.
♪♪
-Hey, yo. Six up.
You piggos, man.
Stride the fuck on, nigga.
-Wazi, we gotta go.
Wazi. Come on.
-You people fuck around,
I will personally bring
my entire squad back through
to boot-fuck all y'all straight
back into your mamas' pussies.
How's that sound?
[ Laughter ]
-Okay. Hold up. Oh.
Thulani...
You ain't never nothing but
one goddamn disappointment
after the next.
Bring white Satan for backup
up in my motherfuckin' house?
-Oh, I'm not backup.
I'm ready to roach spray this
entire fucking sewer on a word.
-Wazi, you cool?
-What's the move here, Xavier?
-"Xavier." [Chuckles]
See you still rockin'
that coon-ass slave name.
-You can miss me with all your
"Black Panther," Zulu bullshit.
Do I look like a kid?
Does it look like I came here
for a fucking lecture?
-Well, you damn sure
don't look like no man.
[ Chuckles ]
You look like
a little piglet to me.
Zulu named Thulani,
but he chose "Xavier"
and a swine's path.
LAPD over his own peoples.
-Waz, you're in a lot
of fucking trouble.
Night Patrol is looking for you.
You ain't hiding
in the Courts.
They'll go through everybody
to get you. Even her.
She killed Pop.
It's just me and you.
We could just dip.
-My son ain't going nowhere.
And I told you,
you ever show your face around
here again, I'll kill you.
Useless-ass pig.
-I don't wanna fight.
-Come in here
wasting my fucking time.
I don't give a fuck
what you want.
-Go at a cop, see what happens.
-Rivette, why do you
keep fucking shit up?
-No, no, no.
Fuck this Crip bitch
and all her little
gangbanger fuckboys.
I don't give a good goddamn --
-Annoying-ass fucking pig!
LAPD murdered one of
our people just last night!
This the message
you can take back to 'em!
Stay they fuck ass
out the Courts, or
else they can get it, too!
Now, ain't no way
you leaving with Wazi,
but you and I both know
you ain't walking out
this motherfucker
without us beating the
dog shit out you, neither!
-You going down
for this, Ayanda.
-Oh, they ain't done shit
to me yet, nigga!
♪♪
-Big for nothing --
[ Grunts ]
-Kick his ass!
[ Grunting ]
♪♪
[ Line ringing ]
-Who this?
-Yo, Born, it's Wazi.
That cop
that killed your sister,
he rolling through
the Courts tonight.
Ayanda think all that voodoo
bullshit gonna stop him.
She's trying to throw rocks
at him and shit.
Look, man.
I ain't dealing with all that.
She gonna get all of us killed!
You niggas need to get over
here with some real firepower.
All right?
-[ Sighs ]
All right. Bet.
-♪ I ain't trippin' on nothin',
I ain't trippin' on nothin' ♪
♪ I be trippin' on murder ♪
♪ Yeah, what you trippin' on? ♪
-Hold this.
-♪ I ain't trippin' on nothin',
I ain't trippin' on nothin' ♪
♪ I be trippin'
on murder, yeah ♪
-There you go.
-♪ What you trippin' on? ♪
♪ Thug life never die, nigga,
thug life never die, nigga ♪
♪ So bury me
a motherfuckin' G ♪
♪ And put my motherfuckin'
chopper by my side, nigga ♪
♪ Yeah, and when you send
them shooters at a nigga ♪
♪ Tell them pussy niggas
look me in my eye, nigga ♪
♪ 'Cause when we comin' through,
we leavin' bodies on the news ♪
♪ Channel seven,
channel five, nigga ♪
♪ I'm a rider,
so I ride for my niggas ♪
♪ I'm a rider, so I ride
for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ I'm a rider,
so I ride for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ Die for my, lie for my,
cry for my, shine for my ♪
♪ Grind for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ Thug life never die, nigga ♪
♪ So what, you pussies
down to ride, nigga? ♪
♪ So bury me
a motherfuckin' G ♪
♪ And put my motherfuckin'
chopper by my side, nigga ♪
♪ Yeah, and when you send
them shooters at a nigga ♪
♪ Tell them pussy niggas
look me in my eye, nigga ♪
♪ 'Cause when we comin' through,
we leavin' bodies on the news ♪
♪ Channel seven,
channel five, nigga ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm a rider,
so I ride for my niggas ♪
♪ I'm a rider, so I ride
for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ I'm a rider,
so I ride for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ Die for my, lie for my,
cry for my, shine for my ♪
♪ Grind for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ This how you niggas
supposed to ride ♪
♪ Yeah, this how you
niggas supposed to ride ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ This how you niggas
supposed to ride ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ This how you niggas
supposed to ride ♪
♪♪
-This is a sacred night.
Ethan has joined
our holy mission.
Tonight when you
step on that battlefield,
we show him
how Night Patrol hunts.
No mercy for our prey,
which means we leave
nothing on the plate.
No witnesses!
Tonight, in my son's honor,
we bleed Colonial Courts dry!
[ All cheering ]
♪♪
Rise.
Time to learn
how to use your gift.
[ Heart beat ]
♪♪
-[ Choking ]
-You've become strong
with blood,
purified as it courses
through your veins,
made holy
by his divine providence.
Tonight you are
reborn in his flesh,
made in the image of God.
Though you feed
on the low beasts of the field,
your true fangs will
never touch their unclean flesh.
Now take your rightful place
by my side.
♪♪
-[ Laughs ]
[ Grunts ] Whoo!
Drink your fill tonight, boys!
[ Spits ]
Oh...won't be this good
till the next riot.
[ Laughter ]
[ Laughs ]
-We shall reign over
our master's kingdom together,
as he wills it.
[ Laughter ]
Father and son.
♪♪
-Here's the story
if anybody asks.
The turf war that's been brewing
is finally popping off
at Colonial Courts.
We got the Zulu Block
Gangster Crips
who murdered in cold blood
a female member
of the Piru Fonk Rida Bloods,
and there's been retaliation
killings on both sides.
So we get to go in
under exigent circumstances.
We don't need a warrant.
We already have
our invitation, boys.
And we're not leaving
until those blood tanks
are overflowing.
-Your boy came and told me about
the pigs killing my baby sister.
-Mm-hmm.
-Kinda put his life
on the line to do it.
-I heard.
-Hmm.
They killing Pirus and Crips.
Trying to pop some
shit off between us.
And they think
we dumb enough to do it, too.
-That's no doubt.
-Mm-hmm.
-Way I see it...
some things bigger
than this gang shit.
-What the fuck
you talking about, nigga?
-Come on, blood.
I'm trying
to work this shit out.
Consider this shit a ceasefire.
-For the time being.
-Yep.
-Pigs on their way?
-Night Patrol is.
-[ Scoffs ]
Even fucking better.
-I got skirmish lines
set up every other courtyard
to slow the pigs'
initial assault.
♪♪
-[ Groans ]
[ Coughing ]
♪♪
[ Groans ]
Fuck.
[ Grunting ]
♪♪
-12-Adam 2-1, Dispatch.
Code triple nine.
Need all units in the area
on scene now.
-Copy, 2-2-1.
Lead unit on scene.
All other units
ordered to stand down.
-Who's lead unit?
-Night Patrol.
♪♪
[ Zipper slides ]
[ Grunts ] Don't shoot.
-Partner?
Wazi's holed up
in Colonial Courts.
You good to help me get him?
Something like --
-Huh?
All right. Let's roll.
Yeah. All right.
♪♪
-No witnesses! No survivors!
Hey! Who the fuck
did you think you are?!
♪♪
[ Screaming ]
[ Line ringing ]
-9-1-1. What's your emergency?
-They tryin' to break
into my apartment!
I'm -- I'm at
the Colonial Courts!
-Ma'am, we --
we have sent units out there.
9-1-1. What's your emergency?
-I don't know what's going on!
People are knocking on my door!
Hey! Let me see a warrant!
-They just killed somebody!
-Okay. Now, calm down, ma'am.
Calm down.
I will -- I'll check into that.
-It looks like the police
are coming in,
but I don't know
what they doin'!
They're -- They taking
people out the house!
You better send somebody!
[ All screaming ]
♪♪
-[ Sobbing ]
-Dispatch, Night Patrol
is on the scene.
We've got it from here.
[ Woman screams ]
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
♪♪
-Drink.
Feed.
♪♪
Feast.
Indulge in the sacred hunt.
Gorge yourself.
♪♪
All are prey.
[ People shouting ]
This is your baptism.
Wash yourself in blood.
♪♪
-[ Gasps ] I can't.
-What's up? You sick?
-[ Gasps ]
-Hey!
-Fuck! Fuck! I can't.
-Hey! Partner? Partner?
-I thought I could handle it.
-Hey! Hey! E!
-Get the fuck back.
Stay back.
You know what's
so fucking stupid about this?
I heard what they were.
I heard what they were and got
put on 'em, and intel was good.
I still didn't believe.
Now I'm fucked!
[ Groans ]
I'm fucked. I'm fucked.
-I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about,
but we gotta go.
-Just stay away.
Just leave. Get out of here.
-What the fuck
is wrong with you?!
-Stay back! Stay back!
-What the fuck is wrong --
-Get the fuck back!
-Hey! Hey! No! Come here.
-If you don't let me do this,
I'm gonna hurt you.
-Let me get my brother.
Just go back to the unit.
Just go!
-I'm sorry!
-Drink!
♪♪
-What the fuck?
Zay.
[ Gunfire ]
-Stay vigilant, Damu.
Remember your training.
If they're lizard men,
they got acid tongues
six feet long and shit.
-Hey, niggas!
Chill the fuck out!
-Tag a sigil
on that wall, blood.
-Don't fucking shoot me on Crip.
-Nigga, what?
♪♪
-Hey, hey. He back up!
-What?
Die, motherfucker!
Damn. That motherfucker
kept running.
Fuck.
That's the pig
that killed Preem?
-Yeah.
-Damn.
Damn. He got your brother, too?
Y'all get good.
We huntin' his ass down tonight.
-What? Fuck all that. Look.
I'm finna go get Moms
and get as far away
from the Courts as possible.
-Acting like a little --
-Man, you ain't gonna last
30 seconds out there
rolling solo.
-Sarge, nigga, don't forget
you gotta get your get-back
on them Night Patrollers
for your loss.
-That's right.
-Don't be acting
like a bitch now.
-Look like we all
carving up swine tonight.
-That's right.
-Let's go, nigga.
♪♪
-Yeah, okay.
-Now, here's what's
happening tonight.
My men are gonna
pump enough blood
out of you fucking people
to last us a good long while.
And nobody --
and I mean nobody --
is coming to rescue you
while we do it.
Do you know why?
You know why?
-[ Fence rattles ]
-[ All gasp ]
It's because you people
are dog shit on the heel
of America's boot!
Why would anybody give a shit
if I scraped it off for 'em?
[ All gasp ]
-[ Mocks gasping ]
Bring him over here.
♪♪
[ All scream ]
There's that fear.
[ People sobbing ]
That fear makes the blood go
down smoother than buttermilk.
-Sir, just got word Ayanda's
holed up in her rat's nest.
Looks like
you'll need to step in.
She's been chewing our boys up.
-[ Scoffs ]
You mean to tell me you
can't handle one lowly native?
-They've got
their tribal shit everywhere.
-I am sick of this
ooga-booga bullshit.
♪♪
Let's go.
[ People screaming ]
-Come on. Move your ass.
Get in there, young man.
-Respect your elders.
-Fuck you.
-Fuck you!
-Hey. Just go ahead in.
Now, folks, sit tight,
and, uh, we'll get to
ripping your fucking
throats out shortly, okay?
-What?
-Yeah. Low-key.
♪♪
-What the fuck
are you doing, dickhead?!
[ People screaming ]
We're the same team, asshole!
What the fuck?!
♪♪
-Hello? Trying to see
where Night Patrol posted up.
[ Sour notes play ]
-Shit. My phone.
Phone ain't fucking working.
-[ Groans ]
They jammin' the signal.
Isolate and destroy.
It's textbook
ethnic-cleansing tactics.
These devils go hard.
-One-time still coming
through this motherfucker.
I think it's time we vamoose.
-We ain't going nowhere
till we get some payback
on that demon fuck.
Y'all saw that shit
that happened back there, man.
-Hold up. Is it demons?
Or is it lizard men?
-Nah, nigga. Pigs.
Them pigs that do
too much amphetamine.
-They vampires.
-[ Chuckles ]
Nigga, are you sure?
-Yeah, nigga! They drink blood!
-Well, a lot of foul creatures
of the night drink blood.
That's not necessarily
the decisive factor
for a vampiric classification.
-Sound about right, though.
Yo, Trip, you brought them
silver bullets?
-Hold up, blood.
That -- That's werewolves, man.
You trippin'.
Man, look.
I think we swing through
the south side of the building,
get the jump on them niggas.
If they on some blood-sucking
shit, air they ass out.
Y'all can use your, you know...
holy weapons or something.
Hit 'em with that shit.
-Look, what we need
to do is get to Moms.
All right?
Ayanda. She got a plan.
-If her plan
was to get lit the fuck up,
I'd say things are going
pretty smooth, nigga.
-Yeah, them pigs probably
already ate her alive.
-Look, we ain't
abandoning my moms.
-Abandon what?
She fucking dead, man!
Now, we stay on ol' boy trail
and we get some get-back.
That's our best
fucking option right now.
-So you mean my best option
is to let my mom die
and get killed
by some fucking monsters?
-Yeah. Yeah.
That sound kinda fucked up.
-How do we know
if she's even still alive?
-I just said we not
abandoning her, nigga.
[ Gunfire ]
-Yeah. See?
Look like them
vampire motherfuckers
let Mama get her guns.
Bring y'all asses.
[ Gunfire ]
-Ayanda!
You brought this on yourself!
-Yeah? Well, got that fire
for your ass!
-Oh, shit!
Yeah, nigga! Hell yeah!
-Zulu street Crip!
-Bitch-ass nigga.
He ain't -- Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
-Damn.
-He ain't dead.
Y'all need to get up!
Move! Wazi, run!
[ Laughs ]
-Niggas, y'all got guns!
Do something!
Hey. Hit that cross.
Smoke this nigga, blood.
-[ Growls ]
-You're gonna suck
a motherfucking dime.
Ah, fuck!
-Oh, shit. Tripp!
-Tripp!
-Oh!
Fuck.
-Kill this nigga.
-What the fuck?
-Hey, nigga, help your homie!
-Yo, back up!
-Watch what the fuck you doing!
-I already emptied three mags
in these motherfuckers!
They keep getting the fuck up!
Fucking petty-ass devils.
-Hey. Use that big shit.
Use that big shit!
[ Gun cocks ]
-Move, y'all, move!
-Use that.
♪♪
-No, Wazi, no!
-Shit.
-[ Growls ]
♪♪
-Hey.
Hey. Waz.
-[ Coughing ]
-Yo, yo, yo.
Waz.
I got a knife in my pocket.
Grab that shit.
♪♪
-Oh, fuck.
-Come on, nigga.
Grab the fucking knife, nigga.
-Motherfucker,
move closer, then.
♪♪
Fuck.
-What's up, homeboy?
-Man, fuck you. Get off me.
Get -- Get your hands off me.
Get the fuck off me.
Get your punk bitch ass off me.
♪♪
-[ Chuckles ]
Where the fuck have you been?
Hiding somewhere crying?
Can't handle the hunger, huh?
I knew you'd bitch out.
Oh! You want to take
a bite out of me?
You hearing me in there,
you special-ops pussy?
Sarge, I hope you're watching.
Let's see what your boy's got.
[ Grunts ]
-Come on, nigga.
-Oh, shit! Come on.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go! Go, go, go!
-No, Wazi!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
♪♪
-They exterminating us, nigga!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
♪♪
-[ Growling ]
-[ Choking ]
♪♪
[ All screaming ]
-Stop this madness.
-[ Grunts ]
-Control your blood lust, or
you're no better than your prey.
I chose you for your discipline,
your dedication
to a higher calling.
I pray I wasn't wrong about you.
I've watched you.
Even when you thought
you were alone, I was there.
-What the fuck did you do to me?
Fuck!
-Despite your suffering,
I watched you pass every test.
-What the fuck?!
-I was the angel
on your shoulder.
It hurts.
-[ Choking ]
[ Gagging ]
♪♪
-It hurts. It fucking hurts.
-Now you drink.
♪♪
-No. No.
-Feed and grow strong.
-[ Grunts ]
-Come on.
♪♪
Open her up.
[ Woman sobbing ]
Go ahead and cut her throat.
She's yours.
♪♪
You clearly need
a demonstration.
You are not in control. I am.
-[ Muttering ]
-Drink the blood.
Or I'll do it for you!
-[ Grunting ]
♪♪
-You're going to
heed my commands,
or I promise you, boy,
I will destroy you
before I let you waste
the blessing you've received.
[ Woman grunts ]
♪♪
-Put the pain behind you, son.
Drink.
Drink, Ethan.
-[ Muttering ]
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
-[ Crying ]
-No.
No.
-No! No!
[ Sobbing ]
Thulani! Thulani!
♪♪
-Hey, yo. See? See?
We gots to keep on it.
Make these devils pay.
-Thulani. Thulani!
-Hey, I gots to keep it moving
if y'all just gonna
curl up here and die, man.
♪♪
-Mama, I -- Ma --
-[ Sobbing ]
-No witnesses, no survivors.
I want Ayanda dead.
Drown them in their own blood.
♪♪
Kill the Zulus.
-Mama. Ma.
-[ Sobbing ]
-[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Grunts ]
-That's for Preem,
you hoe-ass bitch!
This Yakub-sucking fuckboy
ain't murkin' no more
Black people tonight!
That "stake in the chest" shit
really worked!
-Ma, these motherfuckers
really vampires.
-I knew they was demons when
I saw them metal fangs in 'em.
This right here, this the reason
that Pork Chop
didn't get through
my Zulu fortifications.
Ancient artifacts
of our peoples.
Our jewelry, our weapons,
our culture.
That's the enemy's weakness.
-Mama, all them twigs
and shit don't work.
They went right past 'em.
-Read the pamphlet, boy.
♪♪
-Oh, yeah. Shit. Say, uh...
"The Obeyofo"...
-Obayifo. Obayifo, nigga.
-Obayifo.
All right, all right, nigga.
Damn!
"Has pink skin, iron teeth,
and feasts on their prey
from the trees above."
-Same shit. Pigs just
motherfucking rewrote it.
-Another word for 'em?
Asanbosam.
Or devil. Or vampire.
And we all know
who fucked up the bloodsuckers
when they came for 'em.
-The Zulus.
-Let me see that shit.
-I already gave you one.
-We was too busy
fucking up shit to be reading!
Hold on.
"The Obayifo feed off
the blood of sleeping victims
and those who shun sleep
to wander with death
in the darkness"?
God damn. Leopard in the hood.
♪♪
What is this? Some Hotep shit?
-One thing the colonizers
all fear? Our Blackness.
-[ Chuckles ]
Hold up. Time-out.
So you talking about
the indigenous magicks
of the Asiatic Black man?
-We was put on this
motherfucking Earth
to fry white Satan to a crisp!
-Yeah. And that's on Crip.
♪♪
-We are to become a dynasty.
Father and son...
ruling for an eternity.
♪♪
Rise and redeem yourself
in my eyes.
These vermin cannot...
will not best you.
[ Clattering ]
-Hey, look,
they got our people in cages,
and it's on us to get 'em out.
♪♪
All right, look.
What we do know --
bullets don't do shit
to these motherfuckers, right?
But a wooden stake
through the chest?
[ Grunts ]
-[ Wood cracks ]
[ Clattering ]
Yeah, it's the only way.
The head, too, nigga.
Everybody know you hit a vampire
in the head or the heart,
and they out of there.
Your third eye be closed
than a motherfucker.
-Hey. Hold up. Nah, man.
I hit that big cop in the head
five motherfucking times.
It didn't do shit.
And I don't even think these
sticks gonna do much neither.
-What?! Use y'all fucking head.
It's their sacred heart.
The blood fuels
the fire in the heart.
You penetrate,
pop that motherfucker,
and you air their ass out
for good.
Everybody know that.
-[ Coughing ]
-Like, nigga,
the ancestors know that.
It's in the pamphlet.
Check it. Look.
"A colonizer's power
derives from his God's blood
and the flame
of his white witchcraft
that now courses
through their veins."
Man, they even got psychic
powers and can fucking fly.
All types of brazy shit.
Fuck we gonna do?
[ Scoffs ]
The Devil is a motherfucker.
-Oh, shit!
I got something at the crib
that can 100% guarantee
handle it.
-Oh, for real?
-100%.
-Okay. Well, what you got, Ma?
Like a flame thrower?
-Unh-unh. Nah.
-Or an RPG?
Some shit like that?
That's what we gonna need.
-Better. Better than all that.
We got to go back to the roots
with this shit.
-All right, but I mean --
Okay, well, if guns don't work,
heavy artillery
ain't gonna do shit
but just piss 'em off
a little bit more.
Can't believe I'm about to
say this dumb-ass shit.
We gonna have to stab
these vampire motherfuckers
right through their heart.
It's the only way.
-I mean, that's actually
the smartest shit
you said all night, nigga.
We gonna have to get
mystical with this shit
if we're gonna stay alive.
-Well, what about sunlight?
Right? That shit soon.
Don't they blow up in that?
-Yeah.
-If sunlight don't kill these
motherfuckers, we all fucked.
♪♪
[ Gasping ]
[ Coughing ]
♪♪
[ Grunting ]
[ Horn blaring ]
-What the fuck?
♪♪
[ Horn blaring ]
[ Horn stops ]
-What the fuck?!
♪♪
-[ Gasping ]
-What the fuck?
♪♪
[ Indistinct shouting ]
-[ Gasping ]
♪♪
[ People screaming ]
-[ Laughs ]
[ Horns blaring ]
♪♪
-Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Goddamn! Stakes don't work?!
♪♪
Vampire rules got
a nigga twisted, homie!
♪♪
Y'all get on.
I got this shit.
Sick motherfuckers.
Eating babies and shit?
-[ Growling ]
-On Piru. This for Preem
and all the dead homies.
This get-back
for all our people!
Fuck the motherfucking
police, homie!
♪♪
-[ Grunts ]
-Motherfucking pig got me, man.
-Shit! Come here.
-[ Laughing ]
♪♪
-The sun's gonna be up soon!
Fry you devils to ash
if you don't get on!
-We can be out here
well past sunrise, bitch!
We are getting in there,
whatever the fuck it takes!
-[ Gasps ]
-Just stay -- stay still.
No, I'm straight. I'm straight.
-Stay still. Just be still!
-I'm straight.
-Be still!
-[ Panting ]
-Sarge: Ayanda!
We're done fucking with you!
Time to end this!
♪♪
Ayanda!
You hearing me in there?!
♪♪
It's Sarge speaking!
We had a deal!
You keep your tribal
African bullshit
confined to your ghetto, we look
the other way on you people!
Well, that's all done now
that you took that shit
off reservation.
And now you and your boy
know too much to live.
-You been killing us!
Been killing us so long,
I don't know what.
You already killed
one of my sons!
-Ah! I thought that cop looked
like your junkie fuck husband!
Your mother ever tell you
about that, Wazi?
You see,
Danny was our bitch boy.
He did whatever we told him to
so long as he got his...
his fix.
-They made me kill your old man.
They made me.
And I -- I did it to
protect you and your brother.
And I'd do it again
if I had to! For you!
-We gotta get -- We gotta
get you some help, all right?
Hold this. Hold this.
-Come out,
and we drink your blood quick!
Or we can just burn you alive
in there, slow.
-Wazi. Look at me.
Look at me. Look at me.
♪♪
They fucked with
the wrong ones now.
We Zulu up in here.
[ Gasps ]
-Mama, I can't.
-No, no.
-I don't --
-No.
Whatever you feeling,
you harness that shit.
You use that shit.
You are my son.
♪♪
[ Panting ]
-Nah, but you ain't dyin',
not until I kill those
weird-ass motherfuckers.
Where the stash at?
-Security room. Uh, closet.
Wazi, listen.
Don't be mad.
[ Chuckles ]
-It's too fucking late.
♪♪
-Shit!
Yeah!
[ Beeping ]
♪♪
I got it!
Fuckin'...
We about to wet these fools up!
♪♪
Yeah.
[ Beeping ]
What the fuck is this?
Ma, what the fuck is this?
What the fuck am I supposed
to do with this?!
Ma, what the fuck am I
supposed to do with this?!
We gonna die!
We gonna...
[ Beeping ]
[ Crying ]
♪♪
I ain't fucking built
for this shit.
All this fucking Zulu shit.
None of it's real!
♪♪
But you never
would've believed that.
[ Whooshing ]
♪♪
And neither do I, really.
[ Speaking indistinctly ]
You fucking with a Zulu now!
♪♪
-Ethan: [ Growls ]
He's controlling me.
Please. I can't stop.
I can't stop. I --
I just ate a woman's brains.
-Damn. I'm so tired of you
vampire motherfuckers!
-Please, please, please help me.
Help me!
♪♪
-Nigga, help you?
Man, fuck you.
-Wazi!
-You killed my mama.
-I didn't. I didn't. I didn't.
-Wazi!
-I'm on your side.
-You killed my brother.
-I'm on your side, I swear.
I'm one of the good ones.
-Come here, Wazi.
[ Laughs ]
-You...
You killed my fucking girl.
You killed everybody!
-Son, you have work to do.
You are Night Patrol now.
Act like it!
-You're right. You're right.
♪♪
Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo!
[ Growls ]
♪♪
[ Growling ]
[ Energy pulsing ]
♪♪
[ Growls ]
-Oh, fuck!
[ Vehicle alarm blaring ]
[ Panting ]
-Let's try this again.
I want to get you
medical attention,
but you need to
give me something.
-Fuck it.
Night Patrol
are the fucking vampires.
They raided the Courts.
[ Grunts ]
Processing our blood
like it's --
like it's a fucking factory.
[ Crunching ]
But you already knew that.
-Vampires in LAPD
long before I got here.
They're still cops.
-Yeah, and you one of them, huh?
-I ain't no fucking vampire.
-So why the fuck
you protecting 'em?
-Come with me.
Watch where you bleed.
♪♪
Here's the thing, kid.
I don't give a shit
about Black or white.
It's about blue.
They're LAPD. I'm LAPD.
Your brother was LAPD.
And you will always be
the one on the other side
of that interrogation table.
♪♪
-You straight
motherfucking evil.
♪♪
Just gonna pin all this shit
on me, huh?
-No. I'm throwing you
to the wolves.
♪♪
It should be unlocked...cuz.
-You spoiled everything for me.
Now you're going to watch me
crack each of your bones
one at a time
and suck the marrow.
♪♪
-All you pig motherfuckers
are so weird.
But I am glad to see you.
You the one that turned
my father into a vampire,
ain't you?
-Your father?
I would never wash one of
your kind in the sacred blood.
-[ Grunts ]
-[ Screams ]
♪♪
-Bitch-ass pig! [ Spits ]
♪ I ain't trippin' on nothin',
I ain't trippin' on nothin' ♪
♪ I be trippin' on murder ♪
-I'm about to fuck y'all up!
[ Grunts ]
-♪ Thug life never die, nigga,
thug life never die, nigga ♪
♪ So bury me
a motherfuckin' G ♪
♪ And put my motherfuckin'
chopper by my side, nigga ♪
♪ Yeah, and when you send
them shooters at a nigga ♪
♪ Tell them pussy niggas
look me in my eye, nigga ♪
♪ 'Cause when we comin' through,
we leavin' bodies on the news ♪
♪ Channel seven,
channel five, nigga ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm a rider,
so I ride for my niggas ♪
♪ I'm a rider, so I ride
for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ I'm a rider,
so I ride for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ Die for my, lie for my,
cry for my, shine for my ♪
♪ Grind for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ Thug life never die, nigga ♪
♪ So what, you pussies
down to ride, nigga? ♪
♪ So bury me a motherfuckin' G ♪
♪ And put my motherfuckin'
chopper by my side, nigga ♪
♪ Yeah, and when you send
them shooters at a nigga ♪
♪ Tell them pussy niggas
look me in my eye, nigga ♪
♪ 'Cause when we comin' through,
we leavin' bodies on the news ♪
♪ Channel seven,
channel five, nigga ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm a rider,
so I ride for my niggas ♪
♪ I'm a rider
so I ride for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ I'm a rider, so I ride
for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ Die for my, lie for my,
cry for my, shine for my ♪
♪ Grind for my niggas, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, this how
you niggas supposed to ride ♪
♪ Yeah, this how you
niggas supposed to ride ♪
♪♪